Novak Oleksandr CV

Ukraine, Sumy, 40030

Mobile: 380971671551, email: NovakNewNetwork@gmail.com

HTML-coder, Web developer in the Sumy State University

I always strive to become part of a friendly and professional team in which I could develop my development skills and learn new technologies in the IT field to achieve team results. Person with a wide range of experiences

Employment history

Freelance IT

09/2007 - 07/2015

- 1. Layout of various site layouts as well as their constituent parts
- 2.Photoshop/Figma
- 3.HTML/CSS/SCSS

Certified trainer in a network of fitness clubs "Sport Life"

10/2015 - 12/2016

- 1.Personal training
- 2. Training work with groups
- 3. Development of individual training programs

Personal crossfit trainer in the SportLand network of fitness clubs

01/2017 - 12/2018

- 1. Development of individual nutrition programs
- 2. Systematic accounting and analysis of achievements results

- 3. Preparation for the competition
- 4. Personal training

Credit inspector in a financial company LLC "ProstoPozyka"

02/2019 - 12/2019

- 1. Analysis of credit applications
- 2. Customer consultations on lending
- 3. Verification of data provided by the client
- 4. Assessment of clients' solvency
- 5. Detection of signs of fraud
- 6. Preparation of reports

Specialist of the software application products group at

Sumy State University

09/2020 - present time

- 1. Work with document templates
- 2. Development of software products
- 3. Work with databases
- 4. Programming
- 5.HTML/CSS/SCSS/Gulp/JavaScript/React/PHP/Python

Education

- 1. Mechanical Engineering College of Sumy State University by specialty "Computer Science" in 2000 2004 (full-time)
- 2. Bachelor's degree in Computer and Information Technology at the Sumy State University in 2017 2020(in absentia)
- 3. Master's degree in Energy Management at the Sumy State University in 2020 2021 (full-time)

Activities and Communities

- 1. Development of a database obtained during the work of a group of solar power plants (work together with the staff of the Sumy State University)
- 2. Sports club of Sumy State University

Language skills

Ukrainian: native

Russian: fluent

English: A2-B1

A little bit about yourself

I love IT. I love to work. I love interesting and creative work. IT – in my understanding – is also creativity, which is based on erudition, a technical mindset, the ability to think extraordinary and creatively, is the ability to find different ways to solve a problem, the ability to find different ways to achieve the desired result – and all this for the sake of conquering the final effective goal!

I really love this kind of work and always immerse myself in it completely and without a trace.

I love to draw, I love sports, I love box, o love to play chess, I love to read books and I really like to just communicate with people on various topics.

Social Networks

Linkedin

https://linkedin.com/in/aleksandr-novak-891474257

GitHub

https://github.com/novak-new-network

Facebook

https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100041288535507

Telegram

@NovakNewNetwork,

https://t.me/NovakNewNetwork

WhatsApp

https://wa.me/380971671551